# **Abraham Perez**

Victorville, California, United States

abedevelops@gmail.com | (909) 636-2637 | github.com/AbeofSpade | linkedin.com/in/abraham-perez-aa7a3b9b

## **SUMMARY**

As a Front-End Developer, I have a passion for creating innovative solutions that improve my technical skills. I have over 9 years of experience as an Independent Distributor, where I build a team of dozens of distributors which got me to the rank of Gold within in the company and I learned new skills of what it took to build a home based business. I also have over 6 years of experience as a Lead Recovery Coach at OCTLC, Inc./Sustain Recovery, where I worked with adolescents struggling with mental health and/or drug addictions. As I had to role model the behavior we expected I helped them learn life skills, create structure in their lives, and presented them to a community of like-minded people through a 12-step program. I am currently improving the skill set of Full Stack Development I've learned in Codecademy and Mimo, which I hold certifications for but I am focused on Front-End development and I am taking another course with Scrimba. I am always eager to learn new skills and technologies, and I am committed to using my expertise to make a positive impact on the world.

## **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Python, SQL, MySQL, PostgreSQL, React, Node.JS, TypeScript, Git, Leadership, Goal setting, Time Management, Team Building, Communication

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

### **OCTLC**, Inc./Sustain Recovery

Nov 2017 - Mar 2024

Anaheim Hills

Lead Recovery Coach

- Led a team of staff in an inpatient youth recovery home, providing structure, healthy habits, and emotional support to youth struggling with addiction, trauma, and mental health.
- Supervised clients and staff, ensuring adherence to schedules and reporting observations to therapists and staff after each shift.
- Facilitated transportation and supervision for 12-step program meetings, helping clients connect with relatable individuals to support their recovery journey.

Vemma Jan 2013 - Sep 2016

Independent Distributor

- Recruited and led a team of like-minded individuals to promote and sell healthy alternative beverages, achieving Gold rank within the company.
- Developed time management and goal-setting skills to build a successful home-based business with Vemma.
- Utilized public speaking and cold calling to drive sales and recruit new team members, creating a culture of excitement within the team.

Uber Nov 2015 - Feb 2017

Driver

- Provided a personalized and enjoyable ride experience for passengers by engaging in conversations and sharing music preferences.
- Chose to drive mainly in Hollywood & Beverly Hills to interact with successful individuals and learn new skills.
- Enhanced communication skills and gained valuable insights from passengers' stories and experiences.

## **EDUCATION**

CodeAcademy Nov 2023 - Nov 2024

Full-Stack Developer

Mimo Nov 2023 - Jul 2024

Python Developer

Front-End Developer

## CERTIFICATIONS

Full-Stack Developer

**Python Developer**